sansan.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy | Sansan

Sansan, Inc., a corporation established and existing under the laws of Japan, having its principal office at: Aoyama Oval Building, 13F, 5-52-2, Jingu-mae Shibuya-ku Tokyo 150-0001, Japan, Sansan Corporation, a corporation established and existing under the laws of the state of Delaware, having its principal office at 257 Old Churchmans Road, New Castle, DE 19720 and Sansan Global PTE. LTD., a corporation established and existing under the laws of Singapore, having its principal office at 15 Beach Road, 2nd Floor Singapore 189677 (hereinafter collectively called “Sansan”) engages in information management service for corporations and individual customers (compiling business cards into a database, etc.) and has the privilege of contributing to the society. In addition, in view of the advancement of informatization and increasing recognition of privacy in recent years, we believe the proper handling of personal information is now strongly requested. Based on this philosophy, we have set forth the following personal information protection policy, and we will properly handle personal information in accordance with this policy. 

Rules
    The Company shall comply with the laws and regulations, governmental guidelines, and other rules related to the handling of personal information.

Acquisition
    We will acquire personal information in an appropriate manner without using any false or otherwise dishonest means.

Purpose of Use
    When handling personal information, we will specify the purpose of use as much as possible.

Notification
    When acquiring personal information, we will notify the customers of the purpose of use in the event we are required to comply with the provisions of JIS Q 15001: 2006 (hereinafter called “JIS Q 15001”).

Use
    We will handle personal information in an appropriate manner only within the scope necessary to achieve the specified purpose of use, and we will take the necessary precautions for that purpose.

Consent
    When we obtain personal information, change the purpose of use, or gain access to any individual customers, we will obtain the consent of such individual customers in question in accordance with the provisions of JIS Q 15001.

Accuracy
    We will keep the contents of personal information in an accurate and updated condition as much as we can within the scope necessary to achieve the purpose of use.

Safety Management
    We shall endeavor to prevent or correct any unauthorized access, leakage, loss, or damage of personal information and take all other necessary and proper precautions to safely manage personal information.

Employees
    For the purpose of safely managing personal information, we will provide our employees with necessary and proper supervision as well as regular and proper education.

Entrustment
    When we entrust the handling of personal information, we shall endeavor to select a contractor who can fully meet the standards to protect personal information. And in order to strive for the safety management, we shall endeavor to provide such contractor with all necessary and appropriate supervision.

Provision
    Except for cases based on the provisions of JIS Q 15001, we will obtain the prior consent of an individual customer when we provide personal information to third parties.

Disclosure
    In connection with the disclosure of personal information subject to disclosure, we will take the necessary precautions in accordance with the provisions of JIS Q 15001.

Complaints and Consultations
    We will strive to deal with complaints and consultations regarding the handling of personal information in an appropriate and prompt manner and will strive to put in place an organization to achieve such processing.

Audit
    We will regularly audit the status of conformance of our personal information protection management system to JIS Q 15001 and the operating status of our personal information protection management system.

Correction
    We will securely implement corrective and preventive measures for any nonconformities found as a result of the audit.

Review
    In order to maintain appropriate protection of personal information, we will regularly review and endeavor to continuously improve our personal information protection management system.

## Handling of Personal Information

Our policy for handing personal information is as follows: *With respect to the purpose of use of the information used in the Sansan Service, please confirm the same in the Sansan Service Terms of Use, too.

1) Name or Trade Name of Business Operator
    Sansan

2) Personal Information Administrative Manager
    Personal Information Administrative Manager of Sansan.

3) Sharing Personal Information
    a. The extent of entities with whom information may be shared   
Sansan,Inc., Sansan Corporation, and Sansan Global PTE. LTD.
    b. Administrator for shared use   
Sansan,Inc.

4) Purpose of Using and Sharing Personal Information

  * \- To provide Service;
  * \- To deal with customer's inquiries or requests;
  * \- To investigate the customer satisfaction level including the status of use and the environment for use of the Service;
  * \- To provide advertisements and provide guidance on the Service;
  * \- To deliver the e-mail newsletter;
  * \- To analyze the usage of this Service for statistical purpose;
  * \- To use for the marketing activity;
  * \- To provide other guidance and communication.

5) Provision of Personal Information to Third Parties
    The Company will not provide any personal information to any third parties without the prior consent of the customers except in the event such provision is set forth except for the following cases:   
a. Cases in which it is based on laws and regulations   
b. Cases in which it is necessary for the protection of the life, body, or property and in which it is difficult to obtain the consent of the customer.

6) Entrustment
    Within the scope of achieving the Purpose of Use as set forth in paragraph 4 above, when the Company entrusts an outside contractor with the handling of personal information, the Company shall select and supervise such contractor who is capable of proper management of personal information in accordance with the standards of the Company, and the Company will conclude a nondisclosure agreement with such contractor, which is necessary to ensure the safety of personal information.

7) Disclosure of Personal Information Subject to Disclosure and Contact for Inquiries about Personal Information
    At the request of the customers, the Company is ready to receive the customers requests for notification of the purpose of use, disclosure, revision, or addition of the contents, suspension of use, deletion, and suspension of provision to third parties of personal information subject to disclosure in the possession of the Company (hereinafter called “Disclosures, etc.”). For further details about the counter for receiving Disclosures, etc., see the following Personal Information Complaints and Consultations Counter.

8) Voluntariness in Providing Personal Information
    The provision of personal information is voluntary.

9) Acquisition of Personal Information in Manner in which Individual customer Cannot be Easily Identified
    a. The Sansan Service Website may use Cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies (hereinafter called “Cookies, etc.”) and acquire information regarding the state of usage by the customer and the customer’s attribution information in order to protect the customer’s privacy, to enhance the usage, to distribute advertisements and to acquire statistical data. The Cookies, etc. do not contain personal information and they cannot be used to identify the customer.
    The Company uses behavior targeting advertising service provided by the following companies by way of using Cookies in order to optimize the distribution of advertisement to the customer. If the customer wants to invalidate these services, the customer can access to each of the following webpages of the companies and follow the procedures.
    Google Inc.   
The customer can opt out of the service at the following website.   
<http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/ads/>
    Yahoo! Inc.   
The customer can opt out of the service at the following website.   
<https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/us/en/optout/>
    Facebook, Inc.   
The customer can opt out of the service at the following website.   
<https://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/>
    LinkedIn Corporation   
The customer can opt out of the service at the following website.   
<https://www.linkedin.com/help/linkedin/answer/65451/-?lang=en>
    b. Sansan may automatically create and save information such as the IP address, type of browser and browser language of a User who uses Sansan service of digitizing business card data or visits Sansan's webpage. Sansan may use such information to analyze user environment, to offer better services, and to prevent unfair acts which disturb normal provision of Sansan service.

10) Personal Information Complaints and Consultations Counter
    Personal Information Complaints and Consultations Counter of Sansan, Inc.   
Mail address:Aoyama Oval Building, 13F, 5-52-2, Jingu-mae, Shibuya-ward, Tokyo, 150-0001, Japan   
Email address:[info@sansan.com](mailto:info@sansan.com)
